♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
(crowd yelling and screaming)
There it is,
you guys.
The best roller coaster
in all of Quahog.
The League of Extraordinary
Gentlemen: The Ride.
You know, I think they kind
of figured that movie
was going to turn out
to be bigger than it was.
Oh, come on Lois,
it'll be awesome.
It simulates all the fun of...
of, um...
w-what was it now?
It was like a... like a
tall guy in a black hat
and a cape or something?
Yeah, yeah, and there
was the guy
with the
mask who wore a mask.
And one guy
had an umbrella.
Yeah, and I believe he
opened it at one point.
Yeah, and it
wasn't overly long.
Yeah, not-not
overly long.
Sorry, sir, there's a weight
limit on this coaster.
Oh, really,
what's the limit?
The rule is you can't
look hilarious
on this motor scooter.
(laughing)
I'm sorry, there's
just no way.
Big news out of Six Flags
Columbus today,
as they unveil
what promises to be
the largest roller coaster
in the United States.
That's right, Joyce.
They call it The Holocaust.
The ride has several
Jewish groups up in arms...
as they go over
the first rise.
(chuckles)
No, I'm-I'm kidding.
They're actually pretty upset.
Wow.
I had heard about
the Holocaust,
but I never believed it
till right now.
I have to ride
that ride.
Peter, come on, they're not
going to let you that ride either.
You're overweight.
Yeah, if you want to
ride that roller coaster,
you're going to have
to go on a diet.
A diet, huh?
All right, well,
how's that work?
Well, I suppose
you can start
by keeping a
food journal,
like Quagmire does.
Yeah, in fact,
I got it right here.
"Today I ate peaches...
ginger...
honey... candy... olive..."
You know what?
This is the wrong list.
All right, if that's what it
takes to ride that ride,
I am going on a diet.
And I'm not stopping
till I look as good as my
great Aunt "Legs-Go-All-The-
Way-Up" Griffin.
Hey, baby, do those legs
go all the way up?
Why, yes, they do.
(screaming) Oh, my God!
You're a monster!
Come back.
My legs are shaved
like a little girl.
Hey, what do you
got there, Peter?
Rice cakes.
Never had one, but
somebody told me
this is a really good
way to start your diet.
(screaming)
(coughing and gagging)
(retching)
Who...
who could think of such
a horrible thing?!
(evil laughter)
We know you not like
rice cake.
♪ Ricey, ricey rice,
no one like rice cakes. ♪
(gong chiming)
All right, Peter, the
most important thing
when you're on a diet
is willpower.
Now I'm going to put
this steaming pie
on the windowsill to cool.
Now no matter how many
beckoning fingers
that steam morphs into
or how badly it tries
to sneak its way up your nose,
I want you to resist the urge
to levitate
off the ground
and float towards the pie.
Doesn't seem too hard.
All right, go
stand over there.
(laughing)
No, you don't.
No, no,
you can't go in there.
No, no, stay out of there.
That's my special area!
(screams)
No, stop!
I'm saying no!
(screaming)
What kind of pie is this?!
Peter, it's making me watch!
Peter, I don't understand why
we have to drive all the way
to Ohio to ride a
stupid roller coaster.
Yeah, besides, they're still
not going to let you on.
You haven't actually
lost any weight.
Oh, I think my lithe figure
would suggest otherwise.
A girdle is not a substitute
for weight loss, Peter.
Hey, I'm riding
that roller coaster,
and that's all
there is to it.
Now let's get out of here.
This thing's squishing
all my organs around.
(heart beating)
There it is, kids.
Columbus, Ohio.
Now remember, there
are no rules
about who can wear
stretch pants here,
so you're going to see
some pretty shocking things.
Brian, is this
our vacation?
Yeah.
Oh.
Are we trash?
Kind of.
Oh.
I'm sorry, sir. You're too fat
to ride the coaster.
Aw, darn it.
Yeah, why don't you go back
to your pond, hippo?
(laughing)
How about me, sir?
Am I too fat to ride?
No, you don't seem to be.
(laughing crazily)
Well, you got
to hand it to him.
He had a dream
and he made it happen.
That's what
the Wright Brothers did.
So, how's your boyfriend,
Orville, doing?
Ex-boyfriend,
if you don't mind.
And who cares?
He's probably off
in a barn somewhere
working on a contraption
with that weird brother of his.
Ew.
(both laughing)
ORVILLE:
Ha-ha, bitch.
You're so pretty. I miss you.
(gears grinding)
(crashing, people screaming)
PETER: Well, this has given me
a lot to think about.
WOMAN (screaming):
My son is dead!
We are going to have
to send that family money.
I know we are.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Can we stop
and get some food?
Well, I guess it is
close to dinnertime.
Chris, Stewie,
you hungry?
(yawning)
What are you looking at?
You going to propose?
What?
Yeah, exactly.
"What?" Eyes front.
(engine sputtering)
What the hell?!
(loud hissing)
Looks like it's the radiator.
Well, we're just going to have
to find a local mechanic.
On a Friday evening?
I don't think we're going to
have any luck till Monday.
Besides, probably not a lot
of mechanics around here.
So, we're stuck here?
Hey, Lois, you see
that barn out there?
You know who
it was built by?
♪ By... Mennonites. ♪
Well, I guess we better see if
there's a hotel or something.
I can't believe we're
stuck in Amish country.
Yeah, I thought
something was "a-mish."
Hey, uh, excuse me, fella?
Yeah, we're looking for a room.
Are ye indeed, outsiders?
We do not see many of
your folk in these parts,
but we welcome all of God's
children in their hour of need.
Well, actually, I think we need
it for more than an hour.
Or do we, right, Lois?
I-I do not last very long.
Ugh, creepy. What's this?
It's an Amish doll.
They're not allowed
to have faces.
Has something to
do with vanity.
Looks like a cross-dressing
Cobra Commander.
Who?
He's the head of Cobra.
The bad guys from G.I. Joe.
The guys who oddly
shout the name
of their terrorist organization
as they're attacking.
Guys, we're under attack.
By who?
I don't know.
Cobra!
Oh, it's Cobra.
Oh, of course.
Look, they have the pictures
of the snakes on their planes.
Duke, what have I been
saying for years?
What makes a good
terrorist organization?
Brand recognition.
Mom, I can't stay here.
There's no electricity, no
telephones, it's horrible.
Excuse me.
I assure you,
our community is quite pleasant.
Perhaps I could
show thee around.
(amorously):
Okay.
My name is Eli.
My parents run the inn.
If there is anything we can do
to make your room more plain,
do not be afraid to ask.
Ah, we'll be all right.
A hotel in Amish country
can't be any worse
than staying in a youth hostel.
Hi, I'd like a room.
Uh, preferably one
where I have to sleep
with my bag
taped to my body.
We have one where some Italian
backpackers have laid out
every item of clothing
they own on all of the beds.
Oh, perfect.
Will my bunkmates be
constantly talking about me
in a foreign language?
Yes, they will, sir.
Oh, great.
Uh, also, I'm going to have
some mail delivered here,
and I want it to sit in
that box for four years.
Oh, and what street
is the bathroom on?
So, what do you do
for fun around here?
We do chores and we watch
other people do chores.
Sounds kind of boring.
Alas, there are times
when I feel as if
there is much of life
I am missing.
Yeah, it'd be tough
having no technology.
I don't think I could
live without my iPhone.
You have an iPhone?
Yeah. You've heard of it?
Yes, but only because
people sometimes search
for Amish farms
on their iPhones.
Here comes one now.
Thanks for a fun evening, Eli.
And-and thanks
for being so nice to me.
I think you are the
most fascinating girl
I have ever met, Meg.
Here. I want you
to have this.
Your iPhone?
Yeah.
I made you a playlist
of songs that I like.
Who is this I am hearing?
It's Avril Lavigne.
Why does she shout at me?
I don't know.
Most of my music I just
get pressured to buy.
Thank you for
this gift, Meg.
Eli! What are you doing
with that outsider?
Her name is Meg, Father.
And I was just showing her
our community.
You stay away from her.
She will try
to corrupt you.
That is not true, Father.
Meg is wonderful.
She is an outsider.
She does not follow
the one true path.
You are not to see
this girl again.
Do you understand?
I forbid it.
(dejected sigh)
Yes, sir.
Now come home at once.
And, as for you,
I suggest you stay away
from my son, you harlot.
(sobbing)
Hey, there, young one,
why so sad?
It's just that I really like
this boy, but his dad...
Oh, look out.
(loud smacks)
(screaming)
Sorry, there.
Didn't realize
how long it'd been
since Ol' Dumper
did his business.
He'll be done soon enough.
(smacking continues)
Oh, maybe not.
Doesn't sound
like pooping, does it?
Sounds more like someone
dropping sandwiches
off a rooftop.
Watch out below, right?
Look like Hacky Sacks.
You'll be sorry
if you kick 'em, though.
All righty, well he seems
to be all done now.
You have a good evening...
(smacking resumes)
Oh, my goodness.
He must have gotten into
the chicken feed again.
You'd think they'd know
it wasn't in their diet,
but this is how they find out.
You may want
to close your mouth.
(sobbing)
Meg, what's wrong?
Eli's father,
Ezekiel, said
that I can't see him
anymore! (sobs)
He said I was trying
to corrupt his son!
He did, did he?
Well, that does it!
We are gonna teach
this town how to dance!
Oh, Meg, I'm so sorry.
I'd try to talk to Eli's father
for you, honey,
but I don't know
if it's my place.
Ezekiel wouldn't listen
to you anyway, Lois.
You're a woman.
These people live in
a patriarchal society.
The only member of our family
whose word would carry
any weight
would be Meg's father.
Dad, will you talk
to Ezekiel?
Will you tell him
I'm not trying to
corrupt his son?
Please?
All right, I'll do it.
But don't expect
any miracles.
I'm not good
with confrontation.
Like when I got stuck
behind that giraffe
at the ballgame.
Yeah! Nice hit!
Frozen rope!
Awesome!
What just happened?
Ground rule double! Whoo!
I couldn't
even see it.
Yeah, it was something.
Ducks on a pond!
Let's bring 'em in!
Could you please
sit down?
I am sitting down.
You sit up.
I am sitting up,
but I still can't see
a thing.
Yeah, sounds
like a "you" problem.
Let's go, Sox!
Before we commence
with Samuel Fisher's
barn raising, let us pray.
Dear Amish Lord,
thou looketh sternly down
upon us thine flock,
even though we did not
do anything wrong
and have been doing
chores like (bleep) crazy,
please make us humble,
and deliver us more hardship,
that we may get thick,
calloused hands,
much larger
than other people's.
And grant that we become dull,
like Eric Bana,
who we have never seen,
but are just going
by reputation
because it is your will.
We solemnly believe
that although humans
have been around
for a million years,
you feel strongly
that they had
just the right amount
of technology
between 1835 and 1850;
not too little,
not too much.
Please deliver us
from Thomas Edison,
the worst human being
who ever lived.
And protect us
from those who laugh
at our buggies or our hats
and deliver us
from mustaches.
Amen.
Hey, uh, Ezekiel?
You must be Mr. Griffin.
Look, I-I know you guys are busy
with your barn raising and all,
but, um, you know,
I just wanted to tell you
how much my daughter Meg loves
your boy Eli.
I promise you, she ain't trying
to corrupt him or nothing.
Mr. Griffin,
with all due respect,
we live in two
different worlds.
I must do what is best
for my son... and I have.
Hey, how do we know
what's gonna happen?
For all we know,
Meg might want to Amish herself.
I had not considered this.
I was verily preoccupied
with Eli's corruption.
Plus, it is the time
of the month
when Eli's mother
is on the burlap.
So whaddaya say,
let the kids give it a shot?
Perhaps, Mr. Griffin.
Perhaps.
Good.
Now on another note,
I notice you don't have
a damn lick of music
in this town.
We do not believe in
such ostentations.
Well, I am about
to change your mind.
Introducing rock 'n' roll!
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ I'm on a highway
to hell! ♪
♪ Highway to hell! ♪
♪ I'm on the high... ♪
You are banished from
our community at once!
And take your whore
daughter with you!
How did it go, Dad?
Very well, Meg.
My recollection is that
it went extremely well.
Really?! Oh, my God, Dad,
that's fantastic!
So I-I can see Eli again?
EZEKIEL:
Griffins!
(crowd clamoring)
What's going on here?
Your family must leave
our community
and return to the outside world.
Dad, what's happening?
I thought you talked to him.
Sir, please, whatever your
quarrel is with my husband,
I'm sure it's
probably justified,
but I'm begging you, don't
punish the children for it.
They're innocent in all this.
Innocent, are they?
I found this
in Eli's corn hole!
Well, I... His what?
A compartment in Eli's room
where he stores his corn.
Oh. Well, okay,
whatever you say.
Look, Ezekiel, we would love
to go back to the city,
believe me.
I-I haven't had a drink
in three days.
But our car broke down.
We-we can't go anywhere
until it gets fixed.
I have arranged
to have that taken care of.
This ride's gonna be
so frustrating.
I know.
These horses are
so slow.
Sexy.
STEWIE: Good-bye,
Abraham Lincoln people.
(sobbing)
I'm sorry, Meg.
Eli was the best boy
I'll ever meet.
And now I'll never
see him again.
ELI:
Yes, you will, Meg.
(gasps) Eli.
Eli? What are you doing here?
I could not let you
leave without me, Meg.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Hey, Lois, watch me lay rubber
in front of these losers.
Hyah!
Yeah! Choke on that, nerds.
Eli, I agree
that your father was being
somewhat unreasonable,
but I don't think
running away is the answer.
I know, Mrs. Griffin.
And I am sorry.
But I just could
not bear the thought
of never seeing Meg again.
You ever seen one
of these, Eli?
It's a Coleco
football game.
Pretty mind-
blowing, huh?
You know what?
This is garbage to us.
(clattering)
What the hell is that?
Holy crap! Who did this?
It must have been my father.
This is how
the Amish declare a feud.
But I thought they
were nonviolent.
We are,
but Peter must have
really pissed off my dad.
Hey, who raked the leaves?
And look,
somebody mowed the lawn.
I was supposed to do that.
Ha-ha! I have done your chores
to rob you of the joy
of doing chores.
You bastard.
Peter, we don't have
a choice.
We've gotta bring
Eli back.
Oh, no, we don't.
What are you talking about?
We-we can't be part of a feud
with the Amish.
I didn't start
this thing, Lois,
but I'm gonna finish it.
Joe, go round up Quagmire
and all the modern-day
technology you can find.
We are going to war.
Oh. Oh, hey, Bonnie.
Is Joe there?
Well, can I leave
a message for him?
Yeah, it's what I said before
about the-the war thing.
(tires screeching)
(beeping)
All right, men,
this is it.
Technology versus
old-timey wooden stuff.
Let's hit 'em hard.
What, again, was
the nature
of your beef
with them?
I don't know.
Something about
a roller coaster.
Let's go.
Apples... fire!
(all gasping, yelling)
Ah! Damn it!
Ow! God!
Quilters... advance!
Oh! Oh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Ooh! Oh! Ooh! Oh!
I bet this hurts so much!
(screams)
Ow! Damn it! I'm bleeding!
Uhp, now it's an AIDS quilt.
(gasps)
Suck on this,
you furry little weirdoes!
Enough of this crap.
Ezekiel.
Call off your boys and let's you
and me finish this man-to-man.
Indeed.
Prepare for a goodly beating.
(tires screech)
Dad, stop.
Leave him alone.
Father, what are you doing?
I am going to
kill that man.
That man
is my girlfriend, Meg.
(Peter laughs)
This is against everything
our people stand for.
Will you listen to me
for one moment?
You were so worried
about these outsiders
coming into our community
and corrupting me.
But look at yourself.
You're the one who's allowed
yourself to be corrupted.
God in heaven...
you are right.
I am deeply ashamed.
I only wanted to protect you.
I know you did, Father.
PETER:
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
(sighs)
Son, it is your life to live.
I must accept
the life you choose.
I choose to stay here.
What?!
Meg, you are the
most beautiful woman
I will ever know.
You have shown me
so many wondrous things
that have opened my eyes
to the world beyond my home.
But this is where I belong.
I'm sorry
if this upsets you, Meg.
(voice breaking):
I love you, Eli.
I'll always love you.
If this is what you
have to do,
then all I can say is...
I'll never forget you.
(sighs) I am sorry there has been
conflict between us.
Allow me to make amends.
Please help yourself
to anything in my corn hole.
Hey, don't worry
about it.
We can still be pals.
And I know just
the place for us
to go and blow off
all this steam.
♪ We went dancing
across the USA ♪
♪ On that crazy King's Highway ♪
♪ Too much passion ♪
♪ Too much play ♪
♪ We went dancing, dancing,
dancing across the USA ♪
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru